wishafriend.com 2018-12-24

# Wishafriend.com - Privacy Policy

| 

This is the privacy policy for all apps and websites (except Kidlo apps, websites and children apps for which Privacy Policy is available at http://www.kidlo.com/privacypolicy.php) developed and owned by IDZ Digital Private Limited ("IDZ Digital Private Limited", "we", or "us"). We value the privacy of the people who are using the apps, websites and have, thus, created this Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to show our commitment towards safeguarding your privacy. Your privacy is important to us, and we take it seriously. Please read our Privacy Policy below and let us know if you have any questions or other feedback regarding it.

By using our apps, websites or any services linked to them, you agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service. 

**Your data:**  
As a company, we do not collect any Personal Information like email address, birth date or time, age, name, phone number, address, etc., from the users. If we do happen to obtain any personal information, including emails or phone numbers obtained through support requests or other correspondence, it will be treated with the strictest confidentiality. Any such personal information will never be shared with any other entities. Any such personal information will be retained towards resolution of the support requests and for future reference if you need support again. We can delete the emails anytime on your request. We use Google's G Suite for Business for our emails.

Some of our astrology apps or pages on some websites may ask for your birth date, month, time etc. but we do not store any of this information on our servers. The data is processed in your device or computer itself to show you relevant result and not saved anywhere else apart from your device or computer. We do not store any of these details or share the same with any third party including advertising or analytics providers.

**Data for advertising purposes:**   
The below data is collected automatically via advertising providers (except for EU users) and analytics providers   
Your IP address and computer/mobile device identifiers (such as your device ID, advertising ID, MAC address and IMEI)  
Data about your device, such as device name and operating system, browser type and language  
Data collected with advertising cookies   
Coarse location data (country or city-specific)  
Demographic data (such as to determine the coarse location of your IP address)  
Data for advertising and analytics purposes, so we can keep improving our apps

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

The data collected is used to show personalized advertisements depending on your location and jurisdiction. In the European union, the apps are showing non-targeted/non-personalized ads to users after taking their consent. For rest of the world, the data is used to track the content you access in connection with the apps and to deliver, target and improve the advertising.

On most devices you can limit ad targeting from your deviceâ€™s settings. Please review your deviceâ€™s user manual on how to disable ad tracking. In any case, you can contact the advertising providers below and also ask them to delete your data if they have any by opting out.

We use the following ad providers in our apps. All of them are not used on all apps.

AdColony - Privacy Policy <https://www.adcolony.com/privacy-policy/>   
You can opt out or get your data deleted from their privacy policy link.

Facebook Audience Network - Privacy Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation ](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)  
Opt out: <https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences>

Google AdMob & Google Adx: Personal Data collected: Unique device identifiers for advertising. For example, Google Advertiser ID or Apple ID For Advertising.   
Privacy Policy: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>  
Opt Out: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>

AddApptr: Privacy Policy: <https://www.addapptr.com/data-privacy>

**Analytics:**  
We make use of analytics services like Flurry, Google, Appsee, Mixpanel or Facebook that use cookies sent from our app running in your device in order to provide Non-Personal anonymous global data and information regarding app use. The kind of information collected includes the type of device or version of the OS you are using, app crash report, and general pattern of app use. Appsee also records a certain percentage of app sessions in the form of videos without displaying any user input or saving any personal information. We use this data to improve the app and related services over time so that we can serve our users better. It should be noted that at NO point in time shall your Personal Information be linked to the cookies or videos (Non-Personal Information) sent from your device to the analytics services so that your privacy is always kept protected. Flurry, Appsee, Mixpanel and Facebook have their own Privacy Policies for the information they collect from the device via an app. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
The links to their Privacy Policies are given below:

Flurry Analytics Privacy Policy: <https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm>

Appsee Privacy Policy: [ https://www.appsee.com/legal/privacypolicy](https://www.appsee.com/legal/privacypolicy)

Facebook Analytics Privacy Policy:<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

Mixpanel Privacy Policy: <https://mixpanel.com/privacy/>

We may send you push notifications via OneSignal service. No personal information is passed on to them at any point of time.   
One Signal Privacy Policy: <https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy>

**Google Firebase:**  
We use the tool Firebase in some of our apps. This is a real-time database that we use for real-time data exchange and storage in our app to improve and develop our app. The user data is transmitted to Firebase anonymously. Firebase is a Google subsidiary and is based in San Francisco (CA), USA.  
Find the Firebase privacy policy here: <https://www.firebase.com/terms/privacy-policy.html>

In all of the above cases and purposes, we may analyze, profile and segment all collected data in anonymized form.

 **Cookies:**  
We do not set any cookies on your device. Third party advertising or analytics providers mentioned above may set cookies. You may get your data deleted from them via the opt out links provided.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

 **Internet permissions:**  
Our apps do typically require internet permissions, for the purpose of downloading additional content for the app, providing links to the app store entry of our other apps, display advertising wherever applicable and to collect anonymous usage information for analytics as mentioned above.

 **In-app purchases:**  
Our apps may contain in-app purchases (IAP's) or Subscriptions.

 **Social media:**  
Our apps interact with social sites like Facebook, Instagram, Whatsapp, etc to share content from our apps/websites. At no point of time do we collect any information from your social media accounts in any way.

 **Non-Advertising based apps:**  
In case of apps in which no third party ads are there, then the above points related to advertising and ad providers do not apply.

 **Other companies and public authorities:**  
In order to combat fraud and illegal activity, we may exchange data with other companies and organizations and provide it to public authorities in response to lawful requests.  
We may also disclose your data based on your consent, to comply with the law or to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our players or others.

 **OPTING OUT:**  
If you no longer want us to use your IP address and mobile advertising ID then you need to either pay for the in-app purchases to remove advertisements or stop using the apps. As mentioned before, for EU users we are not showing targeted/personalized ads.

For more choices please follow the "Opt Out" link for the respective service above.

 **Age limitations:**  
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal data about or direct or target interest-based advertising to anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use our Services. If you are under 13, please do not send any data about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal data. If we learn that we have collected personal data about a child under age 13, we will delete that data as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any data from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us.  
We do not knowingly contact or do business with children under 13 years of age. If a parent/guardian becomes aware that a child under the age of 13 has attempted to contact and/or do business with us, please advise us by email at support@idzdigital.com so that we may rectify the situation

 **Changes to Privacy Policy:**  
We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time simply by posting such modification on this site and without any other notification. Any such modification will be effective immediately upon posting on this site.   
The use of the information we collect is always subject to the Privacy Policy that is in effect at the time when this information is collected. You are advised to refer to the Privacy Policy from time to time so that you are always in sync with our current privacy practices.

 **Contacting Us:**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.  
IDZ Digital Private Limited  
607, Western Edge II, Borivali East, Mumbai 400066, India  
Email: support at idzdigital.com (Replace at with @ and remove spaces)

This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 30, 2018.
